{"data":[{"question":"Did they deliver your goods safely?     -> Were your goods ................ safely?\n","answer":"delivered","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"56","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"4"},{"question":"People didn't forget his brave deeds.     -> His brave deeds ..................... forgotten.\n","answer":"were not","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"56","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"4"},{"question":"I could see nobody slept in this bed last night.     -> This bed ........................ in last night.\n","answer":"wasn't slept","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"56","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"4"},{"question":"Did you hear that robbers broke into their house last weekend?     -> Did you hear that their house ..................... into last weekend?\n","answer":"was broken","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"56","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"4"},{"question":"Fortunately, they didn't pull down this old theatre.     -> Fortunately, this old theatre ...................... down.\n","answer":"was not pulled","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"56","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"4"},{"question":"Everybody knows it now that the Earth goes round the Sun.     -> It ............................ by everybody that Earth goes round the Sun.\n","answer":"is now known","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"56","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"4"},{"question":"When did Mr Ramsey translate this book into English?     -> When ......................... into English by Mr Ramsay?\n","answer":"was this book translated","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"56","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"4"},{"question":"The government lifted some of the restrictions last year.     -> Some of the restrictions ........................ by the government last year.\n","answer":"were lifted","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"56","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"4"},{"question":"People in our country know Mrs J.K.Rowling's books very well.     -> Mrs J.K.Rowling's books ................. in our country.\n","answer":"are very well known","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"56","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"4"},{"question":"They allow the pupils to speak their language only during Polish lessons.     -> The pupils ....................... to speak their language only during Polish lessons.\n","answer":"are allowed","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"56","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"4"}]}